<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Learnbay blog</title>
        <link>undefined</link>
        <description></description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 10:56:55 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Feed for Node.js</generator>
        <image>
            <title>Learnbay blog</title>
            <url>undefined/logo.svg</url>
            <link>undefined</link>
        </image>
        <copyright>All rights reserved 2023, Learnbay</copyright>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How To Increase The Accuracy Of Machine Learning Model Over 90%?]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The accuracy of machine learning models is the key to achieving the desired and profitable output. Learn how to increase the accuracy of machine-learning models using various methods and strategies.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multimodal Deep Learning | Enabling Fusion of Multiple Modalities And  Deep Learning]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In this blog will introduce you to multimodal deep learning and the process of training AI models to determinate connections between several modalities.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human Activity Recognition With Smartphone]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Human activity recognition (HAR) using machine learning holds a massive hype ad so the projects of human activity recognition using smartphones. Learn how to handle HAR dataset for a project of human activity recognition using smartphones.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fundamentals of Bagging and Boosting in Machine Learning | Ensemble Method]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Bagging and boosting in machine learning are two most popular techniques. This blog will brief you on the various advantages and disadvantages of bagging and boosting.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Top 8 Machine Learning Tools You Should Know in 2023]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[This blog you will learn top 8 machine learning tools and their key features. Every tech industry incorporates ML tools and algorithms into their regular operations.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Create ML and Core ML- The Secret of Apple's Unbeatable Success]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[This blog will brief us about the two Machine learning algorithms, create ML and core ML, which are used by Apple to develop its own IOS tools and platforms.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Does Intelligence Augmentation Differ from Artificial Intelligence?]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the blog, we will learn the major difference between intelligence augmentation and artificial intelligence as well as deployment, functioning, and use cases of IA.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[OpenAI GPT-3 Revolution- The Thrill of Next-Gen AI Innovation]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In this blog post, we will explore all the potential implications of Open GPT-3 and how it helps increase results and productivity]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Are The Differences Between Deep Learning and Neural Networks?]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In this blog, you will learn the key differences between deep learning and neural networks, which will assist you in determining which approach is best for your needs.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Top 5 Machine Learning Projects for Beginners in 2023]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Check out the top 5 ML projects for beginners in 2023.These projects will help to get started with ML and understand the real-world ML problems in a better way.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Top 3 Python Libraries for Machine Learning!]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Python has become a key tool for ML algorithms. In this blog, we'll explore python libraries for ML, that help you to work in different types of ML based projects.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Types of Machine Learning Models - Quickly Explained]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In this blog, you will learn about types of machine learning models that you need to know, which will help you to easily comprehend their work patterns and use cases.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Can MLOps Techniques Help Bring Advanced AI Into Mainstream Business?]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The combination of ML with Devops remains cutting edge while launching a machine learning operation. In this blog, we'll build an MLOps process that combines machine learning (ML) with DevOps to accelerate and automate Intelligent App deployment.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Top 10 Deep Learning Algorithms to Master in 2023]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read on to learn more about deep learning algorithms with best practices and benefits that are able to make predictions, find data patterns, and make decisions.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[10 Must-Know Machine Learning Algorithms for Beginners in 2023]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Machine learning algorithms are essential aspects of designing real-world applications. Reading this blog will quickly assist you in adapting all ML algorithms.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[OctoML- The Coolest Platform for Faster Machine Learning Model Deployment]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Know what is OctoML, How to Machine Learning should be integrated with Apache TVM. Also learn about the how doe OctoMl Works.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is ML Fairness Indicator?- All You Need to Know]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Google's new ML fairness indicator is designed to help developers assess the fairness of their machine learning models. In this article, we'll explain what the ML fairness indicator is and how it works.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stock Prediction Gone Extraordinarily Precise - An Outstanding Application of ML]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Many people have tried to predict stock market performance. In this blog we have discussed algorithms for predicting stock markets]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introduction To Vertex AI Models - The New Horizon of Google Cloud's Success]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn more about the power of Vertex AI models and explore the new horizon of success with Google Cloud in this blog]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[7 Best Machine Learning companies to work for in Bangalore 2023]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Bangalore is one of the best places to work for AI & Machine Learning Professionals, and discover a list of the top 7 machine learning companies to work for in 2023.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No Code Machine Learning Just Gone Viral!- But What's That?]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Machine Learning with no code is a subset of Machine Learning. No code Machine Learning uses a development platform with a code-free drag and drop interface, which is basically grounded on ML and AI-based models.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Future of Education in hands of Machine Learning]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Machine learning allows computers to learn from data without using programs or human interference. This blog will brief you on machine learning in education examples.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regression techniques in Machine Learning]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ML has become a trend in today's world of technology. There are different types of regression techniques in machine learning, which we will learn about in this article.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Necessity of Machine Learning in Retail]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In this blog, you will get an overview of use cases of machine learning in retail that help analyze user habits and make predictions without human intervention.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is Supervised, Unsupervised Learning, and Reinforcement Learning in Machine Learning]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn more about Machine Learning Algorithms, such as Supervised, Unsupervised and Reinforcement Machine Learning. Also, learn their importance in relevant fields.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Normal and Gaussian Distribution]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In this blog you will learn the basics of the normal distribution in statistics by estimating probability distribution and probability.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Everything About the XGBoost Classifier]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In this blog, learn about the XGBoost classifier and how it works with various applications to increase its efficiency.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Everything About Decision Tree From Scratch]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Decision tree is a decision support tool that uses a tree-like model of decisions and their possible consequences, including chance event outcomes, and utility.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introduction to Simple Linear Regression in Machine Learning]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn the fundamentals of simple linear regression in machine learning. Understand how it works, its applications, and implementation]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Top 50 Interview Questions of Machine Learning]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Prepare for your interview with our 50 most asked interview questions of ML. These questions cover a wide range of topics and will help you demonstrate your ML skills.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Linear Regression in Machine Learning]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Linear regression is one of the simplest and most popular machine learning algorithms. It is a statistical method used for predictive analysis.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Random forest model(RFM)]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Random Forest Model is also a classification model with the combination of the decision tree. The RFM algorithm is a supervised classification algorithm.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Support Vector Machine]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Support vector machines are a particularly powerful and flexible class of supervised algorithms. In this blog, we will explore the support vendor machines.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clustering & Types Of Clustering]]></title>
            <link>undefined/category/machine-learning</link>
            <guid>undefined/category/machine-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Clustering & Types Of Clustering is the process of finding similar groups in data, called a cluster. It groups data instances that are similar to each other in one cluster and data instances that are very different(far away) from each other into different clusters...]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>